A Guide to the Noel Behn papers M1084
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- WRITING
  - "General Story" outlines, "Night Owls", early "Seven Silent Men", "Subject to Change," "Split Image" (in co-authorship with Siv Svendsen), "Act of Treason," un-titled and unidentified fragments, notebooks, miscellaneous notes (typescripts, photocopies of typescripts, some annotated; handwritten materials); 1987, 1991, no date. (Box 154)
  - "The Race for the Lindbergh Killer"; "Sihler III", rough draft; "Ping Pong", "Black Box", Lindbergh case materials; unidentified and untitled fragments, notes, etc.; 1970, 1972, 1980, no date (typescripts, photocopies of typescripts, handwritten notes). (Box 155)
  - "The Night Owls", "Owls Out", untitled fragments (typescripts, some annotated; fragments with notes; photocopies, etc.), no date. (Box 156)
  - "A Third Suspect", "The Shining Man" (fragments), Lindbergh-Hoffman case materials (typescripts, photocopies, related notes and correspondence, etc.); 3/8/1972, 3/1/1989, 12/22/1994, miscellaneous dates, no date. (Box 159)
  - Transcriptions of "Master" tapes, 1984; untitled typescripts, fragments, drafts, notes, no date; editor's notes, Jan 18, 1989; lines and story ideas (notes, clippings, magazines, miscellaneous); "The Death Masters" and "Behn Chronology" (typewritten, no date). (Box 161)
  - "Kiss-Pitch”, "Tarzan of the Tetons," "Sihler," "Ping Pong," "Death Masters," "Tom Bostwick Just Bought God" (typescripts, photocopies of typescripts, notes, etc.); miscellaneous fragments and drafts, untitled; 1970s, no date. (Box 162)
  - "The Great Brinks Robbery", chapters 45-69; "Sihler" and "4th Station" (typescripts, fragments, photocopies of typescripts), 1970s, 1991, no date. (Box 163)
  - "Sihler," "Seven Silent Men - dead matter" (typescripts, photocopies of typescripts), 1971, 1983-1984; Lindbergh case materials (mostly photocopies of miscellaneous documents), miscellaneous dates. (Box 164)
  - Lindbergh and "Color Crime" research materials (photocopies of various documents, mostly clippings, 1930s). (Box 165)
  - Lindbergh and "Color Crime" research materials (photocopies of various documents, mostly clippings, 1930s); "Dr. Ross" [?] case research materials, 1920s; "The Shadow Boxer," untitled ["Night Owls"] typescripts, annotated, no date. (Box 166)
  - "Seven Silent Men - dead matter", 12/7/83; "Night Owls", miscellaneous fragments, no date; "A Minor Matter of Retribution," no date; other miscellaneous fragments, typescripts, photocopies of typescripts, some annotated. (Box 167)
  - "Seven Silent Men," "The Kremlin Letter," "A Minor Matter of Retribution," untitled fragments (typescripts and photocopies of typescripts, some annotated), 1966, 1983-1984, no date. (Box 169)
  - "I, Spy", 1996; "A Present from Your Old Man", no date; Lindbergh materials; untitled fragments, no date; related editor's letters, outlines, miscellaneous (typescripts, notes, photocopies, etc.). (Box 174)
  - Books with numerous handwritten notes, marks, etc.: The Spirit of St. Louis by Charles A. Lindbergh (NY, Charles Scribner's Sons, 1953); Bring Me a Unicorn, Diaries and Letters of Anne Marrow Lindbergh (NY, Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, Inc., 1971); George Waller, Kidnap. The Story of the Lindbergh Case (NY, The Dial Press, 1961); Scapegoat. The Lonesome Death of Bruno Richard Hauptmann by Anthony Scaduto (G.P. Putnam’s Sons, NY 1976); The Airman and the Carpenter by Ludovic Kennedy (Viking, 1985); Hour of Gold, Hour of Lead, Anne Morrow Lindbergh, Diaries and Letters, 1929-1932 (Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, 1973); Time Capsule / 1932. A History of the Year Condensed from the Pages of Time (Time-Life Books, NY, 1932). (Box 176)
  - Books with numerous handwritten notes, marks, etc.: The House of Morgan. An American Banking Dynasty and the Rise of Modern Finance by Ron Chernov (Atlantic Montly Press, NY, 1990); The Men Who Robbed Brink's by Bob Considine (Random House, NY, 1961); Brink's! Uncorrected proof, by Noel Behn (G.P. Putnam's Sons, NY, 1977); A Year on the Killing Streets. Homicide by David Simon (Houghton Mifflin Company / Boston, 1991); The Great Depression by Robert S. McElvaine (Times Books, NY, 1984); The Lindbergh Crime by Sidney B. Whipple (Blue Ribbon, NY, 1935); Since Yesterday. The 1930s in America by Frederick Lewis Allen (Harper and Row, Publishers, NY, 1986); Commando Extraordinary. The Remarkable Exploits of Otto Skorzeny by Charles Foley (G.P. Putnam's Sons, 1967); Of Flight and Life by Charles A. Lindbergh (Charles Scribner's Sons, NY, 1948). (Box 177)
  - Russian trip materials and various drafts and versions of the Behn's article on the topic; includes notebooks, maps, postcards, notes, leaflets, travel magazines, etc. (Box 183)
  - Noel Behn's writings - notebooks, drafts, fragments, Lindbergh case materials (mostly photocopies), etc. (Box 185)
- GENERAL FILES
  This series contains research materials, thematic files, FBI materials, off-prints, miscellaneous materials.
  - Thematic files: "Musical and Dramatic Theatre Academy of America" (1963; no date); "Musical Theatre Academy of New York"; "Military Information Enterprises, Inc.", 04/04/96; "Stormfront" (computer printouts from Websites of the "Stormfront" and other racist groups); includes also computer info, various programs, flyers, miscellaneous papers. (Box 14)
  - "Night at the Algonquin" materials: programs, typescripts "Meanwhile, back at the Algonquin…" by Channing Gibson and Tom Fontana, invitations, lists, various drafts, etc. –Nov. 1987; no date. (Box 16)
  - "Algonquin" materials (continued); programs, flyers, Internet printouts (racist and hate sites' materials); "Netscape Navigator Handbook", miscellaneous. (Box 17)
  - "Pentagon on Net" materials (includes printouts etc.), "Simon and Schuster Lawsuit" materials, FBI National Academy materials, actresses' portfolios, miscellaneous papers. (Box 40)
  - Actresses' and actors' portfolios (continued); FBI materials; bibliographical materials on Lindbergh case; off prints; miscellaneous. (Box 41)
  - Actresses' personal files; inventory of the Hauptmann case subject files in the Harold G. Hoffman papers, 1988; a printout related to Hauptmann case, 3/27/1987; "News flash" printouts; Web printouts (criminal info, racist and hate sites, etc.), U.S. Dept. of Justice materials, etc. (Box 49)
  - "Seven Silent Men" promotional materials, events materials ("Seven Silent Men" supper, 1984; "New York Historical Society Banquet," no date; etc.), "To-Do" lists, research materials, miscellaneous. (Box 60)
  - Lindbergh case materials - "Harold G. Hoffman Museum" materials (copies of criminal records, off-prints, copies of related media materials, detective agencies' materials, correspondence, etc.), miscellaneous notes. Folders A1-A33. (Box 61)
  - Lindbergh case materials - "Harold G. Hoffman Museum" materials, continued, folders A34-A102. (Box 62)
  - "The Writers Theatre" file (press releases, invitations, actors' info, grants info, related correspondence, etc.), "The Author Guild, Inc." file; events' files (Mid-Atlantic Mystery Book Fair, 1993; Global Survival Conference, Oxford, 1988); actors' and actresses' portfolios; medical general information; Wilhelm Reich file (a fragment from his biography by Myron Sharaf, photocopies of clippings, W. Reich Museum materials, etc.). (Box 76)
  - Juana Leija case and Hurley Foutenof case materials, 1980s-1990s; Cluna hotels file, 1989, no date; Holocaust Organizations file; Writers' Theatre's mailing list; Writers Guild of America 47th Annual Awards materials, March 19, 1995; books' dust jackets; Tom Clancy's portfolio; actresses' portfolios, Michael Arkin's resume; light diffusion kit; individual's files (Terry George; Leandra Lynn; Andrew Stevovich); miscellaneous. (Box 90)
  - Actors' and actresses' resumes, publishers' catalogs, research materials (thematic files on criminals, fire work, pyrotechnics, impotence, cult movements, mafia history etc. – mostly Internet printouts), N. Behn's 60th birthday list, miscellaneous, 1980s-1990s, no date. (Box 124)
  - Writer's Guild materials, Screen Actors Guild materials, Actors' resumes, miscellaneous indexes and inventories, FBI file, military file, Jan Barry Sandlin case materials, "7 Silent Men" casting and work list materials, miscellaneous (off-prints, printouts, leaflets and catalogs, faxes, letters, etc.); 1950s, 1970s, 1990s, no date. (Box 153)
  - "Missouri Film Production Guide" files; Noel Behn's Cleveland Schedule and related documents; FBI reports, financial documents, etc., 1940s (photocopies); "Writers' Guild" registrations; subject and personal files (Mickey Rourke); John O'Connor, Hall-Mills murder; miscellaneous. Includes correspondence, typewritten and handwritten materials, leaflets, brochures, photocopies, manuals, etc., 1940s, 1969, no date and miscellaneous dates. (Box 160)
  - Actors' and actresses' resumes; Mid Atlantic Mystery Book Fair documents; Intelligence School documents, 1950 [were marked "restricted"]; "Quad-Stanford 1950" edition (with N. Behn's photo-portrait); personal and thematic files, miscellaneous. (Box 170)
  - Actors' resumes and casting materials; subject files ("Lindbergh, The Crime" - PR materials; cat file; drug dealers' criminal case materials; "The Humanities Prize" for "Homicide" scripts, etc.), event files, miscellaneous; a lot of materials regarding Cindy Wirth's business activities and fitness programs. 1980s, 1990s, miscellaneous. (Box 175)
  - PR materials, resumes and personal files, bibliographical materials, leaflets and brochures, Internet printouts, The Musical Theatre Academy of New York information, Musical and Dramatic Theatre Academy of America information, miscellaneous notes, drafts, fragments, etc.; 1990s mostly. (Box 179)
  - Photo-portraits (mostly Noel Behn's), contact sheets, related materials (notes etc.). Two photos are framed (wooden frames, one with glass, one without glass), no date. (Box 181)
  - Miscellaneous photos, contact sheets, Polaroid photos, two film rolls, and related documents (notes etc.); includes photos of Julie Bovasso, Peter Naas, Noel Behn (on his trip to Russia), Cindy Wirth, among others; mini floppy disks and MT tapes, some transcribed. (Box 182)
  - American Art posters file; Joel Orlansky (1996) file; materials on the topics (World Population Explosion Problem; Ecological problem, etc.) - leaflets, bulletins, photocopies, off-prints, etc.); miscellaneous materials. (Box 185)
- VIDEO AND AUDIO MATERIALS
  This series contains audiotapes and videotapes, interviews etc. (some with identified content).
  - Miscellaneous videocassettes, some with episodes from "Homicide” and some unidentified; a videocassette with B.J. Ward's "Stand-Up Opera" (04/26/1994), "Song of Norway"; audiocassettes and EHG TC-20, VHSC cassettes (mini videocassettes). (Box 87)
  - Miscellaneous videocassettes, including "Tony Kaye Films," "VideoHead Cleaners," "Tyson vs. Hollyfield," "Where Eagles Dare," "Heurik Holm," "Kremlin Letter," various "Homicide" episodes, review copy of the interview with Noel Behn about "Lindbergh Crime," "Noel Behn, Dateline NBC, 12/7/1993," "The Best Man" and unidentified materials; includes also JVC-VHSCXR cassettes (mini video cassettes) and audio cassettes. (Box 88)
  - Videocassettes: "Trial of the Century Symposium, Jan. 21-Feb 8, broadcast on the New Jersey Network," "Sons of Norway," "One False Move," "Bounce Terre Mine," "Bonne Terre, Missouri," "Homicide" episodes; VHSC videocassettes and audiocassettes; videocassettes "Global Forum on Survival, Oxford Univ., England," "ABC Night Life 1/8/1981" [?], "Nova: How Good Is Soviet Science, 4/25/1988"; audiocassettes: "Lunch 7/7/1988 at Cage Cielo," "Child Holocaust," "Dena and Rose, Song Stylist." (Box 89)
  - CDs, diskettes, soft mini floppy disks, four cassette albums (one with the title "Boston trip"), 29 audiocassettes total; 5 videocassettes (titled "HBO: Lindbergh," "Carolyn Beauchamp," "Cold Steal: B. Allen. 1991 / Marianne Hettinger," "Homicide: Episode #203, A Many Splendored Thing," an untitled cassette); some materials are fragile and may need further preservation. Scotch recording tape RB-5 (package); an audiocassette titled "300 Green"; "Baseball trading cards" (an unopened package); a CD "The Beginning of the End" with related materials (an invitation, an envelope), called "Slim File," a folder with 3M diskettes and related descriptions (titled "Homicide," "Foot Note," etc.); handwriting samples and plates (Lindbergh case materials), mostly photocopies (includes handwritten and other materials, too). (Box 180)
- WORKS BY OTHERS
  This series contains manuscripts, annotated texts and proofs.
  - "Seven Silent Men" by Jesse Graham (from the book of the same name by Noel Behn); "Seven Silent Men," Scene Report 2, 3rd draft by Hal Ashby, Sept. 18, 1987; "Seven Silent Men," final version by Hal Ashby, 11/4/87, and "Master"; "Vital Parts," screenplay by Hal Ashby, based on the novel by Thomas Berger; "My Bouffant Hairdo" by Tish Cather, Nov 3, 1997; "Black Snow" by Sir Svendsen; typescripts and fragments of typescripts, a letter. (Box 11)
  - Works and fragments of works by Philip Carlo, Shelley Rusteen Conners, Ben Starr, Kenley Shea, Tony Cinciripini, David Black, William Alton, Graham Greene, Samuel Beckett, Channing Gibson and Tom Fontana - typescripts, a proof, an off-print, 1970s-1990s. Includes also fragments by unidentified authors. (Box 15)
  - Works by David Blum, Aaron Julieu, Rob Weiss, Heidi Kujac, Walter Bobbie, Tom Fontana, Herb Gardner, Bryan Lacey, Robert Porter; "Home Fires": A Teleplay by various authors; "Magazines" by Cindy Lee Brinkendahl and Jonathan Smith-Gault [?] - typescripts, 1989-1994, no date. (Box 26)
  - Works by Tish Coffer, T.N. Berg, Tom Fontana, Bruce Paltrow, John Tinker, Lawrence Herbert, Linola Kelly, Al Shannon, Joe Eszterhas, Channing Gibson, 1989-1998; no date. (Box 38)
  - Works by J.R. Chastain, Tom Fontana (some in co-authorship), Tommy De Vito [?], Christopher Sprinkle, Cynthia R. Wirth, and others. Includes also various submissions, related correspondence, miscellaneous. (Box 48)
  - Works by Hal Ashby, Walter Bobbie, Thomas Fontana, Blaine Novak, Bruce Paltrow, John Masius, James Friend, Robert DeLaurentis, Matt Dillon [?], Allan Torrey, unidentified author(s). (Box 58)
  - "Brinks" drafts by David Zelag Geedman and Bruce Nicolaysen (various revisions); "The Crime of the Century" by Robert W. Lenski; "Heat" by an unidentified author (typescripts, notes), 1975-1977; no date. (Box 64)
  - Works by Tom Fontana, Bruce Paltrow, John Tinker, Monty Diamond, Shane Black, Ian Normann Karlsen, Channing Gibson, Laurice Elehwany, Kevin Richards, Julie Martin, an unidentified author, 1988-1992, no date (typescripts and fragments, some are annotated). (Box 65)
  - Works by Thomas M. Fontana, Joel A. Thompson, Walter Bobbie, Daniel Fried, William W. Wilson, 1979, 1992, 1999, no date (typewritten). (Box 70)
  - Works by Robert Cohen, Tom Fontana, Walter Crittenden and unidentified authors; 1990s, no date (typescripts). (Box 73)
  - Works by Adam Drucker, Greg Antonacci, Kevin Barnes, Mike A. Internicola, Willy Holtzman, William J. Zide, and unidentified authors (typescripts and related correspondence); a photocopy of the book "The Cunning Mulatto…" by Fletcher Pratt. (Box 80)
  - Works by Damien Gray, Tom Benson, Christopher Sprinkle, Siv Svendsen, Channing Gibson, Tom Fontana, and unidentified authors (typescripts, some annotated); 1989-1997; no date. (Box 82)
  - Works by Sydney [?], Lee Theodore, Hal Ashby, Jesse Graham, Tom Fontana, Bernie DeLeo, Ron Swanson; "Homicide," Episode 12, by Anya Epstein; 1986-1998; no date. (Box 98)
  - "Homicide" episodes by James Yoshimura, Bounie Mark, Yaphet Kotto, David Simon, Anya Epstein, Jorge Zamacona, Eric Overmyer, Rafael Alvarez, Julie Martin, Linda L. McGibney; "OZ" episode by Tom Fontana; "Dellaventura" by Frank Abatemarco; "Family Brood," pilot episode, by James Yoshimura and Tom Fontana; 1990s. (Box 99)
  - "Junk Bonds" by Lucy Wang, 7/96; "Homicide" episodes by Henry Bromell, James Yoshimura, Tom Fontana, David Simon, Anya Epstein, Julie Martin, Jorge Zamacona, Darryl LeMout, 1995-1997 (typescripts). (Box 101)
  - "Homicide" episodes by David Simon, Tom Fontana, Michael Whaley, Anya Epstein, Eric Overmyer, Bonnie Mark, Jack Behr, Julie Martin, Kevin Arkadie, James Yoshimura,, Edward Gold, Jorge Zamacona, Michael Chernuchin, D. Maria Legaspi, David Rupel (typescripts, some annotated); 1995. (Box 102)
  - "Homicide" episodes by Jorge Zamacona, Julie Martin, David Rupel, Eugene Lee, Bonnie Mark, Henry Bromell, Tom Fontana, D. Keith Mano, Rogers Turrentine, Jean Gennis, Phyllis Murphy (typescripts, some with handwritten marks and notes), 1994-1995. (Box 103)
  - "Homicide" episodes by David Simon, James Yoshimura, Tom Fontana, Anya Epstein, Julie Martin, Darryl LeMout Wharton, Henry Bromell, Linda McGibney, Philip B. Epstein, Sean Jablonski, Matthew Witten, Eric Overmyer, Gay Walch, Jane Smiley, David Mills, Randall Anderson (typescripts), 1994, 1996-1998. (Box 104)
  - "Homicide," "OZ," "Murder.com" episodes, various pilot episodes and screenplays by Tom Fontana, Yaphet Kotto, Les Carter, Susan Sisko, Ben Hecht, Charles Lederer, Anya Epstein, Lynda LaPlante, Christopher Kyle, Lee Blessing, Jeanne Blake, James Yoshimura, Debbie Sarjeant, and an unknown author; typescripts; 1949, 1996-1998. (Box 106)
  - Works by Frank Pugliese, John Connolly, David Loucka, Barry Levinson, Stephen Metcalfe, Larry Duberstein, Mickey Rourke, Tom Fontana, Bruce Paltrow, John Tinker, S. Lee Pogostin (typescripts, photocopies of typescripts, off-prints); 1986-88, 1995; no date. One material is marked "confidential." (Box 111)
  - Works by Harry Russo, Tom Fontana, David Black, Rob Moss, Clifford Harris, Robert Mark Kamen, John A. Nist, Hiroshi Sugawara, Haruniko Yoshimeki, Jorge Zamacona, 1983; 1994-1995; no date (typescripts and related correspondence). (Box 112)
  - "Homicide" episodes and other works by Paul Attanasio, Jorge Zamacona, Bonnie Mark, James Yoshimura, Tom Fontana, Frank Pugliese, Fredric Brown, and unknown authors (typescripts, fragments of typescripts, photocopies, some annotated, with handwritten marks and notes), 1992-93, 1995; no date. (Box 113)
  - "Homicide" episodes and related materials and other works by Ron Thompson, Jorge Zamacona, Tom Fontana, James Yoshimura, Paul Attanasio, and unknown authors (typescripts, fragments of typescripts, outlines, fillers, related correspondence), 1992-93, 1997; no date. (Box 114)
  - Works (some untitled) by Tom Fontana, Sean Jablonski, Elizabeth M. Cosin, Bradford Winters, Allan R. McKinnon, Orran Farmer, John Kirk, Peter Mattei, Kurt Sinnamon, and unknown authors. Typescripts, 1997-1998; no date. (Box 119)
  - "OZ" and "Homicide" episodes and other works by Elizabeth M. Cosin, Kathryn Paulsen, Andrea Newman, Nabeil Sarhan, Willy Holtzman, Tom Fontana, Joanna Cohen, mums [?], Bronwen Hruska, Juliann Garey (typescripts, related correspondence, resumes), and unknown authors. 1990s, no date. (Box 120)
  - Works by Cindy Wirth, Daniel Weitzman, Marilyn Osborn, Ken Brisbois, Matt Mullin, John Carlen, Randi Cushnir, Jay Clark, Christian Maxwell, Susanna K. Elm, Gene Cogan, Andrew Ordover, muMs the schemer [?], Larry Grossburg, Susan Sullivan [?], et al. (typescripts, photocopies); 1984, 1986, 1997-1998; no date. (Box 127)
  - Works by Dvora Inwood, Robin U. Russin, Sara M. Dexheimer, Lois Johnson, Gary Anderson, Eve Pellegrino, Maryellen Stadtlander, R. Scott Gemmill, Andrew C. Ordover, Steven Berko, Neal Hirschfeld (typescripts and related correspondence), 1996-1997; no date. (Box 128)
  - Works by Aram Saroyan, Tanya Hamilton, Dvora Inwood, Russ La Valle, Richard Sweren, Stephen R. Aisenberg, Sonec Thompson, Clark Middleton (typescripts and photocopies of typescripts, related PR, correspondence), 1995, 1997; no date. (Box 129)
  - Works by Judith McGreary, Marc Kristal, Richard Holland, Tanya Hamilton, Steven Berko, Francine M. Storey, Tim Hotchner, Stephen J. Brackley, Pamela K. Long, R. Scott Gemmill (typescripts and related correspondence); 1995-1997; no date. (Box 130)
  - Works by Andrew C. Ordover, Walter T. Meade, Eve Pellegrino, David Shore, Tori A. Baker, Jodie Blackford, Thomas McKelvey, Amos Kamil, Brian Cameron Fuld, Linda Wright, Tim Minear, Ron Lux, Jonathan Robert Kaplan, and an unknown author (typescripts, related PR and correspondence); 1994-1997; no date. (Box 131)
  - "Homicide" episodes by Frank Pugliese, Paul Attanasio, James Yoshimura, Jorge Zamacona; "A Present From Your Old Man" by Walter Crittenden; "Ascent" and other works by unknown author(s); typescripts, 1992-1994; no date. (Box 135)
  - "Homicide" episodes by David Simon, Anya Epstein, Matt Witten, Paul Attanasio, and unknown author(s), other works by Louisse Bernikow, Kim Philby, Edith Pinero Green, Eric S. mu Mticulous, Catherine Lewis, mu Ms the Schemer, Walter I. Meade, Lorenzo Carcaterra, John Braut, Edith Renaud, and unknown author(s); typescripts, photocopies, uncorrected proofs; 1932, 1970, 1968 [?], 1979 [?], no date. (Box 143)
  - "Homicide" episodes by David Simon, David Mills, Paul Attanasio, Anya Epstein, Tom Fontana; other works by P. Chayefsky, Bob Fosse, Linda M. Wright, Robert A. Furthur [ ?], and unknown author(s); 1978, 1982, 1990s, no date (typescripts, some annotated). (Box 146)
  - "Seven Silent Men" by Hal Ashby, Jesse Graham and unidentified author(s), loose pages, untitled fragments, etc.; typescripts and fragments, some annotated; no date. (Box 149)
  - Works by Timothy Nolan, Candido Tirado, Steve Monroe, Earl Majikau, Dorothy Dellabough, Hal Ashby, Grant B. Dellabough, and an unidentified author; 1987, 1990s, no date (typescripts, related notes and correspondence). (Box 158)
  - Works by Carmen Rivera, McGowan, Guy Durham, A.H. Corliss, Saltzman [?], Jam Tracks, Michael O’Connor, T. Schulz [?], Ch. Bukovsky, D.F. Canning, unidentified authors (typescripts, photocopies, notes, miscellaneous). 1980s-1990s, no date, miscellaneous dates. (Box 172)
  - Works by Bradley Tusk, Cheryl Difalla, Susan Winston, Dan Funk, Greg Zittel, Edward Pomerantz, Julie Friedgen, Jonathan Robert Kaplan, Stephen Evangelinas, Laura Cahill, Carl Ellsworth, Timothy Nolan, Philip John Taylor, Linda Reynolds, Kenya Boone, Robert Duvall, and unidentified authors: typescripts, a book, related correspondence and other materials. 1990s; no date. (Box 178)
  - Works by Aaron J. Schuster, Steven Tanenbaum, and unidentified author(s) - typescripts. (Box 185)
- CLIPPINGS AND MAGAZINES
  This series contains clippings, newspapers, magazines and miscellaneous publications.
  - Magazines, newspapers, clippings and photocopies of clippings, Web news printouts; includes also reviews of Behn's works in printed and electronic media. Mostly 1990s. (Box 21)
  - Clippings and photocopies of clippings including those related to "Seven Silent Men"; miscellaneous magazines including those related to "Ping Pong" research; 1980s-1990s mostly. (Box 55)
  - Magazines and publications ("Time," "Boston," "George," etc.), miscellaneous catalogs. (Box 56)
  - Magazines, newspapers ("The Hollywood Reporter," "The New York Times Book Review," etc.), miscellaneous press releases, clippings, photocopies of clippings, publicity materials, etc. (Box 63)
  - Magazines and publications related to "Ping Pong" and "Lindbergh" research; miscellaneous clippings and photocopies of clippings; "New York," "New York Times Magazine"; "Computer Tooter"; 1980s-1990s mostly. (Box 79)
  - Newspapers accounts on Lindbergh case (photocopies and negative photocopies of clippings). (Box 97)